<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
<channel><title>Kiiwiis.xyz</title><link>https://kiiwiis.xyz/index.html</link>
<description>Dumb stupid shit made by a deumb stupid person</description><language>en</language>
<lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 02:32:07 -0500</lastBuildDate>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 02:32:07 -0500</pubDate>
<atom:link href="https://kiiwiis.xyz/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
<item><title>
Archival project: UMD Movies
</title><description><![CDATA[

<p>Hello everyone! I recently got a PSP for the first time and have been loving it so far! I heard that there were movies for the PSP so I thought 
it'd be neat to get some archived versions of it but couldn't seem to find any! So I decided to start my own archival project for them! I am going 
to start collecting as many UMD movies as I can and when I get a new addition to my collection I'll back it up and store it online (privatley 
though, don't want sony to come knocking down my door lol). I <i>will</i> however have a table of all the movies I have backed up with the 
checksum and size of the .iso file when ripped! I'm really hoping that one day I can get a community going for this archive project where users 
can add to the backup and we can have a full table of all the movies and TV shows! I've ordered my first to "movies" (really they're TV shows) and 
they are Jackass Vol 2 & 3! They were the cheapest on ebay when I bought them so that's why :p</p>
<br>
<p> I'll be sure to update about this when I can!</p>

<p>Tags: <a href='tag_archival.html'>archival</a>, <a href='tag_PSP.html'>PSP</a>, <a href='tag_UMD.html'>UMD</a></p>
<!-- text end -->
]]></description><link>https://kiiwiis.xyz/archival-project-umd-movies.html</link>
<guid>https://kiiwiis.xyz/./archival-project-umd-movies.html</guid>
<dc:creator>Kiiwii</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 02:32:04 -0500</pubDate></item>
<item><title>
Hello!
</title><description><![CDATA[

<p>This is my first blog post on my personal website, there will most likely be more to come!</p>

<p>Tags: <a href='tag_hello-world.html'>hello-world</a></p>
<!-- text end -->
]]></description><link>https://kiiwiis.xyz/hello.html</link>
<guid>https://kiiwiis.xyz/./hello.html</guid>
<dc:creator>John Smith</dc:creator>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 02:15:04 -0500</pubDate></item>
</channel></rss>
